<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <title>Explore China Guide</title>
  
  <subtitle>China 144-hours travel guide</subtitle>
  <link href="http://example.com/atom.xml" rel="self"/>
  
  <link href="http://example.com/"/>
  <updated>2023-09-15T05:23:56.000Z</updated>
  <id>http://example.com/</id>
  
  <author>
    <name>wukong</name>
    
  </author>
  
  <generator uri="https://hexo.io/">Hexo</generator>
  
  <entry>
    <title>144-hours trip to China? These china facts you should know</title>
    <link href="http://example.com/2023/09/14/2023-09-14-144-hours%20trip%20to%20China?%20These%20china%20facts%20you%20should%20know/"/>
    <id>http://example.com/2023/09/14/2023-09-14-144-hours%20trip%20to%20China?%20These%20china%20facts%20you%20should%20know/</id>
    <published>2023-09-14T13:36:20.000Z</published>
    <updated>2023-09-15T05:23:56.000Z</updated>
    
    <content type="html"><![CDATA[<p>When traveling to China, you’d better know some basic information about China.</p><ul><li>Full Name: The People’s Republic of China</li><li>Chinese Name: 中华人民共和国 (Zhōnghuá Rénmín Gònghéguó)</li><li>Area: 9.6 million square kilometers (3.71 million square miles)</li><li>Population: 1.37 billion (as of 2014)</li><li>Capital: Beijing</li><li>National Flag: Five-Star Red Flag</li><li>Location: Central and East Asia, bordered by the Pacific Ocean to the east</li><li>Territorial Waters: Bohai Sea, Yellow Sea, East China Sea, and South China Sea</li><li>Climate: Predominantly continental monsoon (Tibet has a vertical climate zone)<br>-People: Han Chinese (93.3%), plus 55 ethnic minorities like the Miao, Li, and Mongols</li><li>Language: Mandarin Chinese (Putonghua) based on the Beijing dialect, along with various regional dialects</li><li>Major Religions and Beliefs: Officially atheist; also Confucianism, Buddhism, Taoism, Islam (over 22 million), Catholicism (over 4 million), and Protestantism (over 10 million)</li><li>Currency: Renminbi (Yuan)</li><li>Government: People’s Congress System</li><li>Administrative Divisions: 23 provinces, 5 autonomous regions, 4 municipalities, and 2 Special Administrative Regions</li></ul><p>China, an ancient, enigmatic, and beautiful country, has always attracted adventurous foreign visitors. As the third-largest nation in the world, it covers 9.6 million square kilometers and spans 62 degrees of longitude and 49 degrees of latitude. Its diverse landscape and climate give rise to numerous natural wonders. </p><p>China is also rich in resources, plants, animals, and minerals, which have sustained countless generations of its people.<br><img src="/../images/china-facts-great-wall.png"></p><p>China takes pride in its vast population, ancient history, vibrant culture, and distinctive customs. Among its most notable contributions to the world are the “Four Great Inventions”—paper, gunpowder, printing, and the compass.</p><p>Chinese arts and crafts, such as painting, calligraphy, opera, embroidery, and silk production, are unique and deeply rooted in tradition. Martial arts, or Kung Fu, which have recently gained popularity globally, have been integral to Chinese culture for centuries. </p><p>Chinese literature reflects the country’s rich cultural heritage. And, of course, Chinese cuisine, beloved and enjoyed around the globe, remains a key aspect of its cultural legacy.</p><p><img src="/../images/pandas_eating_bamboo.png"></p>]]></content>
    
    
      
      
    <summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;When traveling to China, you’d better know some basic information about China.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;ul&gt;
&lt;li&gt;Full Name: The People’s Republic of China&lt;/li</summary>
      
    
    
    
    <category term="China travel" scheme="http://example.com/categories/China-travel/"/>
    
    
    <category term="china travel" scheme="http://example.com/tags/china-travel/"/>
    
    <category term="china 144-hours" scheme="http://example.com/tags/china-144-hours/"/>
    
    <category term="china beijing" scheme="http://example.com/tags/china-beijing/"/>
    
  </entry>
  
</feed>
